<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="card_category_events">Events</string>
    <string name="card_category_excursions">Excursions</string>
    <string name="card_category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="card_category_places">Places</string>
    <string name="cost_string">Cost</string>
    <string name="dialog_share_label">Share...</string>
    <string name="dialog_share_option_share">Share...</string>
    <string name="events_balley_address">Dekabristov av., 34a</string>
    <string name="events_balley_cost">from 2000 to 6000 rub.</string>
    <string name="events_balley_title">\"Yaroslavna. Eclipse\" ballet on the second stage of Mariinskii Opera house</string>
    <string name="events_cheese_address">Iliyushina av., 14</string>
    <string name="events_cheese_date">15-16 february 11:00-21:00</string>
    <string name="events_cheese_title">Cheese Weekend Cheese Festival at Dolgozernoye</string>
    <string name="events_cheese_description">On February 15 and 16, all cheese lovers will once again gather in the Dolgozeryny shopping mall, because it is where the Cheese Weekend will take place - these are two days of tasting farm products in an exciting festival format.</string>
    <string name="events_balley_description">Boris Tishchenko’s ballet based on The Tale of Igor’s Regiment, choreographed by Vladimir Barnabas.</string>
    <string name="excursion_secret_cost">4600 rub. per group up to 4 people</string>
    <string name="excursion_secret_date">1 january - 29 february 10:00-18:00</string>
    <string name="excursion_secret_description">A photo walk through the iconic non-tourist places of the city on the Neva, allowing you to feel the local flavor.</string>
    <string name="excursion_secret_title">Excursion \"Secret Petersburg: a walk with the photographer\"</string>
    <string name="excursion_top_cost">700 rub. per person</string>
    <string name="excursion_top_date">1 january - 29 february 11:00-21:00</string>
    <string name="excursion_top_description">The roofs offer breathtaking views of the main attractions of the Northern capital. You can admire the panorama of the city and evaluate its architecture on the excursion \"Petersburg: a view from above.\"</string>
    <string name="excursion_top_title">Excursion \"Petersburg: top view\"</string>
    <string name="food_indian_address">Aptekarskiy av., 4</string>
    <string name="food_indian_date">daily 11:00–22:00</string>
    <string name="food_indian_description">7 Spice is an Indian street food with an open kitchen, exciting flavors and a modern, minimalist design. There are no tusks of an elephant or a maharaja diamond, but there is a spiritual atmosphere, a bright interior and dishes from brand chef Jimmy Singh.</string>
    <string name="food_indian_title">Indian Street Food \"7 Spices\"</string>
    <string name="food_pivo_address">Yujnaya doroga st, 15</string>
    <string name="food_pivo_cost">1500 rub.</string>
    <string name="food_pivo_date">mon–thu, sun 12:00–0:00 fri, sat 12:00–1:00</string>
    <string name="food_pivo_description">Feel yourself in an old German fairy tale without leaving the region. There will be in St. Petersburg a house stylized as a Bavarian suburb, and a beer garden, and a small author\'s brewery.</string>
    <string name="food_pivo_title">" Restaurant-brewery \"Karl and Friedrich\""</string>
    <string name="food_rynok_address">Iliyushina av., 14</string>
    <string name="food_rynok_date">daily 11:00–22:00</string>
    <string name="food_rynok_description">The reconstructed agricultural market is now a newly designed fresh market, where for customers there are departments with goods from almost all corners of the world. This type of market destroys all ideas about the familiar concept of “market” - now it is a modern conceptual platform where you can always get to know something new and not worry about the quality of the purchased goods.</string>
    <string name="food_rynok_title">Gastronomic market \"Dolgoozerniy\"</string>
    <string name="places_oleni_address">Liningradskaya region, Mendsary city, Lesnaya st., forester\'s house</string>
    <string name="places_oleni_description">A picturesque reindeer farm hidden in the forest invites guests and residents of the Northern capital to get acquainted with the amazing companions of Santa Claus.</string>
    <string name="places_oleni_title">Reindeer Farm \"Forest Hut\"</string>
    <string name="places_planet_address">Obvodniy canal, 74</string>
    <string name="places_planet_date">daily 10:00–22:</string>
    <string name="places_planet_description">In Planetarium No. 1, everyone can touch the cosmos. The dome of the new planetarium is a giant screen. The image is transmitted to him by forty powerful projectors. The special inclined design of the dome allows visitors to take impressive shots against the background of stars and galaxies.</string>
    <string name="places_planet_title">Planetarium No. 1</string>
    <string name="share_provider_all_title">Share link using...</string>
    <string name="like_action">Liked!</string>
    <string name="dislike_action">Disliked!</string>
</resources>